{
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 4,
      "prompt": "______ is a tool that transpiles JSX into valid JavaScript.",
      "answers": [
        "React",
        "Babel",
        "Webpack",
        "ES6"
      ],
      "correctIndex": "1"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "prompt": "What syntax makes it possible to unpack values from arrays, or properties from objects, into distinct variables?",
      "answers": [
        "spread",
        "key-value",
        "coalescing",
        "destructuring"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "prompt": "Returning different elements from a component depending on the state of your application is known as _____ rendering.",
      "answers": [
        "voodoo",
        "conditional",
        "reactive",
        "controlled"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Nerd",
      "answers": [
        "e",
        "2",
        "kn",
        "knld"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0,
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Nerd",
      "answers": [
        "e",
        "2",
        "kn",
        "knld"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0,
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "prompt": "fgsfdgs",
      "answers": [
        "sdfsfgsdfg",
        "fgsfdgsdfg",
        "fdgsdfg",
        "sfasdfasdf"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0,
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "prompt": "fgsfdgs",
      "answers": [
        "sdfsfgsdfg",
        "fgsfdgsdfg",
        "fdgsdfg",
        "sfasdfasdf"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0,
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "prompt": "fgsfdgs",
      "answers": [
        "sdfsfgsdfg",
        "fgsfdgsdfg",
        "fdgsdfg",
        "sfasdfasdf"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0,
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "prompt": "fgsfdgs",
      "answers": [
        "sdfsfgsdfg",
        "fgsfdgsdfg",
        "fdgsdfg",
        "sfasdfasdf"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0,
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "prompt": "fgsfdgs",
      "answers": [
        "sdfsfgsdfg",
        "fgsfdgsdfg",
        "fdgsdfg",
        "sfasdfasdf"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0,
      "id": 13
    },
    {
      "prompt": "fgsfdgs",
      "answers": [
        "sdfsfgsdfg",
        "fgsfdgsdfg",
        "fdgsdfg",
        "sfasdfasdf"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0,
      "id": 14
    },
    {
      "prompt": "fgsfdgs",
      "answers": [
        "sdfsfgsdfg",
        "fgsfdgsdfg",
        "fdgsdfg",
        "sfasdfasdf"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0,
      "id": 15
    }
  ]
}